SUMMARY

Web Developer with extensive experience in all areas of advanced web development. Experienced with user interface, testing, and debugging processes. Providing experience in web system design, implementation, testing, and maintenance. Having a varied and promising skill set. Expertise in a variety of technologies, including Java, C#, C++ JavaScript, and Microsoft SQL Server.

EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern

May 2023 - July 2023• As a software engineering intern at Talent Serve, I actively participated in all phases of the software development life cycle, including requirement gathering, design, coding,

- · As a software engineering intern at Talent Serve, I actively participated in all phases of the software development life cycle, including requirement gathering, design, coding, testing, and deployment.
- · I gained firsthand understanding of software development frameworks, tools, and programming languages such as Java and Node.js.

Social Entrepreneurship internship

Hamari Pahchan NGO May 2023 - June 2023

- · Facilitated social activities and outings for clients, increasing their social involvement and personal growth possibilities.
- · Social media APIs have been integrated to allow users to share content across several social media platforms.

PROJECTS

How sunny is it?

https://today-is-c5dx.onrender.com · July 2023- July 2023

• The "Weather Website" utilizes JavaScript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, and Node.js to provide users with real-time weather information for their desired city. The website's front-end is built using HTML, CSS, and jQuery, while Node.js powers the back-end, enabling data retrieval from weather APIs and seamless communication between the front-end and back-end

Friend Connect

https://tree-reyy.onrender.com/ • July 2023 -July 2023

· FriendConnect is an innovative web project that combines user registration with social connections and leverages the power of Mailchimp for seamless email integration. It

Drum Kit

https://jeonjungkook01091997.github.io/drumkit/ • July 2023 -July 2023

·Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, JavaScript with Event Listeners (addEventListener), and possibly Node.js with Express.js for backend.

DICE_GAME

https://jeonjungkooko1091997.github.io/Dicee_game-/ · June 2023 - June 2023

·The "Dice Rolling Game" is an engaging web application that leverages the power of JavaScript, HTML, CSS, and jQuery to create a fun and competitive gaming experience for two players.

SIMON GAME

https://jeonjungkook01091997.github.io/simon_game/ · June 2023 - June 2023

• The "Simon Game" is an exciting memory-based game that combines HTML, JavaScript, Bootstrap, CSS, and jQuery to create an interactive and visually appealing gaming experience

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology, CSE

National Institute of Technology, Hamirpur \cdot 8.24 \cdot Hamirpur, H.P \cdot 2024

High School

Mount Carmel School • 9.25 • Palampur • 2020

Matriculation

Mount Carmel School · 9.3 · Palampur · 2018

CERTIFICATIONS

Hamari Pahchan

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1IIqUBLk6CpBeJB1YSNorylNzC86ywEno/view

Namma Yatri Open Challenge

https://unstop.com/certificate-preview/e65822e1-c49b-4a24-ad3c-862e21b81cc3?utm_campaign=site-emails

Tata Crucible Campus Quiz 2023

https://unstop.com/certificate-preview/09dc7500-ca34-45b7-b36a-ada09f522459

Advanced Software Engineering at Walmart USA

 $https://www.linkedin.com/posts/jyousana-688379225_forage-activity-6971055776521949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_medium=member_desktop \cdot 20221949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_medium=member_desktop \cdot 20221949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949185-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 2022194918-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share\&utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share@utm_member_desktop \cdot 20221949-yhPb?utm_source=share@utm_source=sha$

Software Engineering at J.P Morgan

SKILLS

Technical Skills: C++, C#, Front End, Backend, Web, Html Css, Javascript, Javascript Jquery, Angularjs, Reactjs, Nodejs, Rest, Springboot, Mongo Db, Java, Backend, Javascript, Html, Node Js, Jquery, Browser, CSS, My SQL, HTML5, Node.js, SQL, Git, GitHub, Programming, DOM, Bootstrap, Unix, api, EJS, Databases, mongoose, robo3T, authentication and security, web3, blockchain, software logic, DSA.